export default {
  id: 'low_1006_5_2b',
  name: '상용한자(5학년-2/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:うけたまわ(る)/음:しょう', answer: ['承'] },
    { question: '독:しめ(す)/음:じ、し', answer: ['示'] },
    { question: '독:알/음:しき', answer: ['識'] },
    { question: '독:まなこ/음:がん、げん', answer: ['眼'] },
    { question: '독:누를/음:あつ', answer: ['圧'] },
    { question: '독:진/음:えき', answer: ['液'] },
    { question: '독:ひたい/음:がく', answer: ['額'] },
    { question: '독:さくら/음:おう', answer: ['桜'] },
    { question: '독:あま(る)、あま(す)/음:よ', answer: ['余'] },
    { question: '독:やさしい/음:えき、い', answer: ['易'] },
    { question: '독:さか、さか(らう)/음:ぎゃく', answer: ['逆'] },
    { question: '독:펼/음:えん', answer: ['演'] },
    { question: '독:も(える)、も(やす)、も(す)/음:ねん', answer: ['燃'] },
    { question: '독:なが(い)/음:えい', answer: ['永'] },
    { question: '독:いとな(む)/음:えい', answer: ['営'] },
    { question: '독:あず(ける)、あず(かる)/음:よ', answer: ['預'] },
    { question: '독:갈/음:おう', answer: ['往'] },
    { question: '독:얼굴/음:よう', answer: ['容'] },
    { question: '독:지킬/음:えい', answer: ['衛'] },
    { question: '독:은혜/음:おん', answer: ['恩'] },
    { question: '독:こた(える)/음:おう', answer: ['応'] },
    { question: '독:옳을/음:ぎ', answer: ['義'] },
    { question: '독:うつ(る)、うつ(す)/음:い', answer: ['移'] },
    { question: '독:더할/음:えき、やく', answer: ['益'] },
    { question: '독:よ(る)/음:いん', answer: ['因'] },
    { question: '독:まか(せる)、まか(す)/음:にん', answer: ['任'] },
    { question: '독:재물/음:し', answer: ['資'] },
    { question: '독:섞일/음:ざつ、ぞう', answer: ['雑'] },
    { question: '독:は(る)/음:ちょう', answer: ['張'] },
    { question: '독:ふたた(び)/음:さい、さ', answer: ['再'] },
    { question: '독:あ(る)/음:ざい', answer: ['在'] },
    { question: '독:재물/음:ざい、さい', answer: ['財'] },
    { question: '독:わざわ(い)/음:さい', answer: ['災'] },
    { question: '독:かたき/음:てき', answer: ['敵'] },
    { question: '독:길쌈할/음:せき', answer: ['績'] },
    { question: '독:맞을/음:てき', answer: ['適'] },
    { question: '독:ぜに/음:せん', answer: ['銭'] },
    { question: '독:た(える)、た(やす)、た(つ)/음:ぜつ', answer: ['絶'] },
    { question: '독:つ(ぐ)/음:せつ', answer: ['接'] },
    { question: '독:ほど/음:てい', answer: ['程'] },
    { question: '독:なさ(け)/음:じょう、せい', answer: ['情'] },
    { question: '독:まつりごと/음:せい、しょう', answer: ['政'] },
    { question: '독:정할/음:せい、しょう', answer: ['精'] },
    { question: '독:きわ/음:さい', answer: ['際'] },
    { question: '독:절제할/음:せい', answer: ['制'] },
    { question: '독:지을/음:せい', answer: ['製'] },
    { question: '독:さ(げる)/음:てい', answer: ['提'] },
    { question: '독:할아버지/음:そ', answer: ['祖'] },
    { question: '독:つく(る)/음:ぞう', answer: ['造'] },
    { question: '독:가지/음:じょう', answer: ['条'] },
    { question: '독:つみ/음:ざい', answer: ['罪'] },
    { question: '독:준할/음:じゅん', answer: ['準'] },
    { question: '독:ま(す)、ふ(える)、ふ(やす)/음:ぞう', answer: ['増'] },
    { question: '독:증거/음:しょう', answer: ['証'] },
    { question: '독:えだ/음:し', answer: ['枝'] },
    { question: '독:こころざ(す)、こころざし/음:し', answer: ['志'] },
    { question: '독:ささ(える)/음:し', answer: ['支'] },
    { question: '독:직분/음:しょく', answer: ['職'] },
    { question: '독:お(る)/음:しょく、しき', answer: ['織'] },
    { question: '독:바탕/음:しつ、しち、ち', answer: ['質'] },
    { question: '독:도울/음:さん', answer: ['賛'] },
    { question: '독:캘/음:さい', answer: ['採'] },
    { question: '독:せ(める)/음:せき', answer: ['責'] },
    { question: '독:つま/음:さい', answer: ['妻'] },
    { question: '독:まね(く)/음:しょう', answer: ['招'] },
    { question: '독:다/음:そう', answer: ['総'] },
    { question: '독:きず(く)/음:ちく', answer: ['築'] },
    { question: '독:はか(る)/음:そく', answer: ['測'] },
    { question: '독:법칙/음:そく', answer: ['則'] },
    { question: '독:こころよ(い)/음:かい', answer: ['快'] },
    { question: '독:모습/음:たい', answer: ['態'] },
    { question: '독:す(べる)/음:とう', answer: ['統'] },
    { question: '독:しりぞ(く)、しりぞ(ける)/음:たい', answer: ['退'] },
    { question: '독:やぶ(る)、やぶ(れる)/음:は', answer: ['破'] },
    { question: '독:판단할/음:はん、ばん', answer: ['判'] },
    { question: '독:판목/음:はん', answer: ['版'] },
    { question: '독:あ(む)/음:へん', answer: ['編'] },
    { question: '독:평할/음:ひょう', answer: ['評'] },
    { question: '독:ぬの/음:ふ', answer: ['布'] },
    { question: '독:あば(れる)、あば(く)/음:ぼう、ばく', answer: ['暴'] },
    { question: '독:たわら/음:ひょう', answer: ['俵'] },
    { question: '독:ゆた(か)/음:ほう', answer: ['豊'] },
    { question: '독:かわ/음:か', answer: ['河'] },
    { question: '독:하례할/음:が', answer: ['賀'] },
    { question: '독:かぎ(る)/음:げん', answer: ['限'] },
    { question: '독:と(く)、と(かす)、と(ける)/음:かい、げ', answer: ['解'] },
    { question: '독:ゆる(す)/음:きょ', answer: ['許'] },
    { question: '독:けわ(しい)/음:けん', answer: ['険'] },
    { question: '독:あらわ(れる)、あらわ(す)/음:げん', answer: ['現'] },
    { question: '독:도울/음:ご', answer: ['護'] },
    { question: '독:ま(じる)、ま(ざる)、ま(ぜる)/음:こん', answer: ['混'] },
    { question: '독:き(く)/음:こう', answer: ['効'] },
    { question: '독:たし(か)、たし(かめる)/음:かく', answer: ['確'] },
    { question: '독:あつ(い)/음:こう', answer: ['厚'] },
    { question: '독:おこ(る)、おこ(す)/음:こう、きょう', answer: ['興'] }
  ]
}
